Let's go.
I'll see you
next time.
When your body will disappear,
I will not be able to die.
Hell no, I will not be able to die!
But you had to throw the scout boss.
Down for the count little bomber just
neutralized the guy hiding on the cliff good.
I'll go find out who it
was hold it a buck yo
This beach could be crawling
with pursuers eager to end us.
We're here for one reason only
it's imperative We begin a replay
of the man who photographed
Trish's mother here 15 years ago
The longer we stay, the greater
risk we're bound to face.
Yeah, but there was only
one guy hiding on the cliff.
Ucharate, don't you remember the stand
we both encountered when on the plane?
Mista turned the user into a bullet-ridden
heap for all the good it did.
We need to figure out
who the hell that is,
or we're just asking for
trouble to follow us.
Narancia, can you confirm his death?
No, not at the moment.
But his breathing's getting
fainter and fainter.
He hasn't moved at all.
All right.
Narancia and I will go investigate.
Abakio, start using Moody Jazz
pronto and begin a replay.
I'm on it.
Just bear in mind we can't linger here.
How much time do you think you'll require?
For nearly two decades?
Eight to ten minutes if I'm being hopeful.
You'll get it done in five.
Meaning lookouts are necessary.
Giorno, Trish, and Mista are needed.
The very second Moody Jazz reveals the
boss's true identity, we get the hell out.
Narancia, use Lil' Bomber.
Let the others know we need them out here.
Right!
Finally, I've solved the mystery.
I know who you are.
Your true self.
before i expire let me see it your
real face apologies but i cannot
allow this conversation to continue
risotto nero bujarati and his crew
cannot be allowed to know about me
take pride in yourself though you
were a true warrior and led the hitman
team well You shall die with honor.
Your team will say the same
when you meet in the afterlife.
Your life will come to an end soon.
But Bucciarati is also here
and is on his way to find you.
So before you slip away, return the
iron nutrients you ripped from my body.
In exchange, I shall take it
upon myself to lay you to rest.
Don't you want to avoid the
embarrassment of a slow, painful death,
especially at the hands
of Bucciarati's crew?
The very murderers who took the
lives of your dear teammates.
Such abject weakness would only bring shame
to them as they rest in the beyond. I...
won't... die...
What are you muttering?
You'll have to speak up.
All I want from you is
my iron risotto, Nero.
I'm telling you that I'm not dying alone.
Isstan may inflate my
flesh, but it all works out.
Because those chunks, the ones with my
essence that are scattered everywhere,
will let me use them to drag you to hell.
Now fire, Lil' Bomber. Die.
The hell?
What's with Lil' Bomber?
Dammit!
The stronzo stuck himself to my stand!
Emperor Crimson.
I've only obliterated time by
half a second everything that
occurred during that time has
been removed leaving behind
the result of the remaining
half second and to spare you the
suspense that'd be the bullets
ripping through your flesh!
Bravissimo risotto nero you embrace death
honorably yet even with
you out of the picture?
My circumstances remain far from ideal.
What now?
I have to do something.
You sure, Narancia? Absolutely.
Something burrowed into Lil' Bomber.
Shit!
So they've come.
At last.
I have to get out of sight.
I'll hide for now and
replenish my stolen nutrients.
Let's hold here.
We must tread carefully now. Got it.
Looks like we're good to go.
There's no question his breathing
stopped, and his stand is gone too.
This guy's deader than dust.
He's gonna be tough to ID.
I think I overdid it and mauled the guy.
I think it's safe to say he's
the head of the Hitman team.
How can you tell?
He came here solo, so he was
either an elite assassin,
or regardless of personal skill,
the sole survivor of a decimated squadron.
Not only that, there was
another competent killer here,
one who got in his way and ended his life.
Uh, not to question your sleuthing skills,
but I was the one who littered
his corpse with those holes,
so?
- No, you were merely a pawn.
We're not alone on this battlefield.
What?
Look at his foot.
Little bomber would have
inflicted severe burns,
but that wound shows no
sign of any such injuries.
meaning the limb was torn from his body.
But how?
Lil' Bomber only picked up one
living body on its scanner.
I'm still not getting another signal.
And besides, why would anyone do
something so foul in the first place?
Well, it stands to reason.
Both combatants were blindsided, so the
survivor is out there licking their wounds.
Though how they're concealing their
breathing is still a mystery to me.
Narancia, have you already
alerted Giorno and the others?
Yeah, they're heading to the
place the picture came from.
Then we'll follow after them.
From here on, we're tracking
anything that draws breath,
even if it's as small as a mouse.
Our mystery killer is still in the area.
They're an extremely dangerous
member of the Family.
Damn it.
This is inconceivable.
Sardinia's my birthplace.
I won't see it sullied by that scum.
I know we're outdoors, but this is crazy.
If I up the sensitivity so that
it picks up frogs and rodents,
I'll have no accuracy.
Not to mention,
if I mess with the range too much,
the radar is going to start registering
random tourists and car exhaust.
Screw it!
I'll just shoot down
everything in the area!
That's enough!
The frogs and mice will no doubt be
hiding in the shadows and burrows.
Their skittish movements
will be totally different.
Set your sights on someone
clearly on the run. Huh?
Right, they'll be trying
to leave the area.
No time to lose.
I have to stop him.
Bakio can't use it.
is a cursed stand.
There, dead ahead.
Hey, where are Narancia and Bucciarati?
Could be wrong here,
but I only see Abacchio.
There must have been an enemy.
They're likely in pursuit now?
and it seems Abacchio still
hasn't gotten his replay.
to the time period that we need.
Trish knows the photograph was
taken 15 years ago in June,
but she has no recollection of
the specific date in question.
Moody Jazz is using its timer.
To pinpoint the exact time when
it obtains that information,
it'll take the form of the boss.
Let's move out.
Hey, let's play over here.
You're the goalie today.
No way.
Rock paper scissors. Then.
Well, then have you found them?
Got him, Bucciarati!
I'm sure it's the enemy!
I'm picking up a signal 80
meters to our right, down there!
They're moving slow, but they're making
their way straight for the tourists!
Narancia, I need you to hold back!
Whoever the enemy is,
we need intel on them.
He completely stopped moving!
Bucciarati?
What?
Listen, you have a choice to make.
But just know I'm prepared to kill you.
If you're no longer capable of combat,
I command you to show yourself.
You have my word, you'll live.
I'm giving you three seconds. Got it?
Your time's up and your life is forfeit!
Superman!
Where are you looking?
I'm over here!
It's not my fault that you suck! Whatever.
Just get the ball and move.
Why don't you get it?
It's already the 25th.
June's almost over.
What's the deal?
Does it better be the right
damn June 15 years back?
Come on! Higher! Higher!
Throw some rocks!
Shake the branches or climb up higher!
Could you brats shut the hell up?
Play your stupid little
game somewhere else.
We're almost done, geezer.
Who even kicked it up there?
Would you quit it with the rocks already?
You're gonna have to reach harder.
Yeah, I know!
But this is as far as I can reach!
Enough. Just move it. I'll do it myself.
What the hell is going on?
What is this? Hold on!
Don't attack him, Narancia.
He's just an ordinary kid.
One of the tourists.
His mouth is sewn shut!
And with his shoelaces!
This has to be the work
of the enemy stand user.
They must have switched places.
The boy's complexion tells me whoever
it is has lost a lot of blood.
Question is where did all the blood go?
Where did this child
abusing monster run off to?
How'd they vanish into thin air?
They were practically dead seconds ago.
I don't know.
None of this makes sense.
Thanks! Come on!
Ah, nice!
Gracias, senori! Gracias, senora!
Thanks for your help!
See you later!
Thanks for your help and everything!
Wait up! Thank you!
There's just no place like home.
I'm on a roll.
Let's go!
We get right this time!
Hey, there was Norfolk!
What was your name again?
The Fates Countdown!
uh do you need some
help down there officer
sorry to interrupt you i'm
here on an assignment looking
for fingerprints there was a
robbery across the street last
night poor Fool got struck
with a bottle and the pieces
went flying everywhere some even
went clear past the sidewalk
including the piece he was holding
appears the suspect through something
over here and I think it landed in
this bin I'm sure I'll find a set
of prints here so that's the part
I'm on the hunt for so you're really
gonna look through them all it comes
with the job I see guess you're right
uh say uh gone well just
so i know for my own
information don't take
this the wrong way i'm
just curious but what
will you do if you don't
find any prints it's very
likely that you won't
we're still what do you
do if you do find him
and the bastard just
gets some dirty lawyer
who still gets him off
scot-free what's your
next move i mean how do
you keep going after that
good questions i keep going because
i have a greater end goal if the
outcome is your focus then it's easy
to look for shortcuts and ultimately
shortcuts keep you from seeing the
truth it drains your spark for life
what matters most is your will to
seek the truth despite the outcome
As long as you keep that in mind,
it doesn't matter if he
gets away on this Grand.
Justice always has its day.
And that's what we're
really fighting for, right?
I envy your will.
For as long as I can remember,
I wanted to be a cop.
Even as a kid, I dreamed of becoming
the most respectable officer I could be.
Back then, I also had the
kind of will you possess now.
However, I screwed up big time.
There's a word for folks like me.
We're utterly hopeless.
We never see things through to the end.
And our shortcomings
always lead to failure.
You couldn't be more wrong, Abakyo.
The path you're on is righteous and just.
Our will is the same.
That will you possessed when you were
only a fledgling police officer remains.
It still burns inside you as brightly
and dutifully as ever, Abbacchio.
But how…
how could you possibly know my name?
Hang on just a second.
I have this feeling we've
met before, but where?
Where are you going, Abbacchio?
I'm getting on that bus.
It's all coming back to me now.
That's right.
I have to get out of here.
I have to help my comrades
with what's coming.
Have you forgotten, Abakyo?
You came here on that bus.
It's a last stop, I'm afraid.
There's no going back. Not ever.
Wait. It's you.
All along, it was you.
I took that damn bribe
and you paid the price.
Oh, Abakyo, you've done
so much good since then.
Hear me when I say, I am
so proud of you, amiko mio.
Oh god, no!
It's not real!
It's not!
It can't be!
You have to heal him, Giorno!
What are you waiting for? Fix this!
Do something before I kick your ass!
I'm sorry, but it was an
instant kill at close range.
We just didn't...
we didn't make it in time.
How could you do it, Ipaccio?
How could you let the enemy
get close enough to do this?
Mista, make sure Trish
stays in the turtle.
It's highly likely our foe's next
move will be to come after her.
We have to escape.
It's not safe for us here.
This tragedy's my fault.
We're getting out of this place.
Our investigation has ended.
What are you trying to
say here, Bucciarati?
Abacchio's gonna wake up any second!
Just you wait!
It'll take time, but he's coming back!
Give him a chance to wake up!
Tell him I'm right, Giorno!
Isn't that what happened before?
Hey, come on!
That is enough, Narancia!
We have to leave this instant.
Bring out Little Bomber and
start scouting an escape route.
What the hell are you saying, Bucciarati?
You're not making any sense right now!
They want to face the bastards
so I can blow their ass to bits!
If they're nearby, then they
need to come out and face me!
Right, Mista?
Did you know?
Hey, answer me, Mista!
Narancia, we have to go.
Listen to Bucciarati.
No, not you two.
What is wrong with you?
Why are you being this way?
You've never been the guy to
turn your back on a comrade.
You bring him back to us.
Do your friggin' job and start
growing some replacements.
This isn't helping.
Narancia! I don't care!
Oh, fuck you.
So you're just leaving
him here to run, Pucinati?
After everything our group has been
through, how can you just walk away?
Don't ask me to abandon him.
Anything but that, please.
That is a direct order, Narancia.
Abakio was aware of the
risk and did his duty.
We're leaving.
Wait, please, but you're at me!
What's that?
Bucciarati, don't go yet.
Whatever this is, it must mean something.
It has to.
Yeah, but what's he holding?
I can't tell.
Right now, it looks like a normal rock.
But I wonder.
Restore it, Golden Wind!
Return from whence you came.
Hey, take a look at this.
I think Abakio actually
managed to complete his replay.
This must be a death mask.
The replay created it.
Before Moody Jazz vanished, he succeeded.
He used the last of his stand
energy and imprinted this face here.
This pillar is like a lithograph.
Abakio, left behind the
message of a lifetime.
This is the visage of the boss!
Abakio, you've made everyone proud.
Truly, your unrelenting
determination to uncover the truth
has made its way to the hearts
and minds of your comrades.
And that, my old friend,
is all that matters.
Stand up, join us Come on,
just say this a lie We are the power,
those days are future
Cause we are the fighters,
just fighting for a right
Thank you.